<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>viral news on </title>
    <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/tags/viral-news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in viral news on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://angelajholmes.github.io/tags/viral-news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ugly Christmas Sweater Party Invitations 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/ugly-christmas-sweater-party-invitations-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/ugly-christmas-sweater-party-invitations-2021/</guid>
      <description>This is my personal collection of halloween costumes and ugly christmas sweaters.i love building costumes so much that i figured out how to make costumes right into christmas. The holiday party pros at hgtv shares how to go beyond an ugly christmas sweater this year. Price and stock could change after publish.
  20 Ugly Christmas Sweater Party Ideas from styletic.com  Get into the christmas season with this fashionable christmas tree sweater!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hallmark Nightmare Before Christmas Ornaments 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/hallmark-nightmare-before-christmas-ornaments-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/hallmark-nightmare-before-christmas-ornaments-2021/</guid>
      <description>Each mystery bag contains one (1) stylized ornament packaged at random, and comes “blind” packaged in a sealed bag to open at home. Log in to add to cart . Get hallmark disney the nightmare before christmas jack skellington ornament (each) delivered to you within two hours via instacart.
  NIGHTMARE BEFORE CHRISTMAS PUMPKIN KING HOLIDAY TREE &amp;amp; ORNAMENTS | eBay from i.ebayimg.com  2021 hallmark keepsake ornament disney tim burton&amp;#039;s the nightmare before christmas bedtime stories jack skellington available now for fast delivery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Homemade Ornaments 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-homemade-ornaments-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-homemade-ornaments-2021/</guid>
      <description>First, paint popsicle sticks white and let dry. All the materials a diyer needs to create this homemade christmas ornament. Homemade christmas ornaments · mickey mouse · tasty hamburgers · christmas bulbs · vintage christmas postcards · key ornaments · cross stitch · 3d deer .
  35+ Creative DIY Christmas Decorations You Can Make In Under An Hour from cdn.architecturendesign.net  Homemade keepsake ornaments · salt dough handprints · wrapped up photo · time capsule ornament · snowman painted shell · salt dough initials · hand .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charlotte Speedway Lights 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/charlotte-speedway-lights-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/charlotte-speedway-lights-2021/</guid>
      <description>Thursday through sunday it&amp;#039;s $20 a car because they also … 23/11/2020 · regardless of the length of your trip, we think the charlotte motor speedway’s light display should be on your itinerary. A nextgen test which is the new car for the 2022 season has been scheduled for november 17 and 18.
  Speedway Christmas at Charlotte Motor Speedway back for 2019 from i1.wp.com  Speedway christmas is returning to charlotte motor speedway for a.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diy Christmas Cards 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/diy-christmas-cards-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/diy-christmas-cards-2021/</guid>
      <description>Whether you&amp;#039;re postmarking your bundle from sunny florida or under alaskan stars, you&amp;#039;ll be thrilled to make and send out any one of these holiday card diys. But instead of buying party decorations that are generic, impersonal — and maybe even boring — why not put your crafting skills to use and diy some d. Everyone loves a great handmade present, especially when it’s clear how much time, effort and love yo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Background Aesthetic 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-background-aesthetic-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-background-aesthetic-2021/</guid>
      <description>You can also upload and share your favorite aesthetic christmas laptop wallpapers. Multiple sizes available for all screen sizes. The great collection of christmas green aesthetic wallpapers for desktop, laptop and mobiles.
  Harry Potter Christmas Wallpapers - Wallpaper Cave from wallpapercave.com  Multiple sizes available for all screen sizes. You can also upload and share your favorite aesthetic christmas laptop wallpapers. Aesthetic christmas 4k uhd backgrounds. You can also upload and share your favorite desktop aesthetic christmas wallpapers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Heard The Bells On Christmas Day 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/i-heard-the-bells-on-christmas-day-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/i-heard-the-bells-on-christmas-day-2021/</guid>
      <description>Many restaurants are open on christmas day and even offer special meals and deals to patrons. Bells and whistles is a microsoft outlook plugin that adds all sorts of juicy functionality to your email. This emom session hits your chest, abs and legs without any equipmen.
  Christmas Bells â Jennifer Chiaverini from jenniferchiaverini.com  We earn a commission for products purchased through some links in this article.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blue Christmas Decor 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/blue-christmas-decor-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/blue-christmas-decor-2021/</guid>
      <description>Primary, secondary, and tertiary colors. In fact, it’s made up of red, green, yellow, blue and orange. Learn modern decorating tips from camille styles, a target style expert.
  Awesome Christmas Tree Decorations from fluxdecor.com  Are you looking for health insurance? These colors occur naturally in nature and are on the light spectrum, so no color combine to make blue. Blue tones decorate these beautiful homes. Katarzyna bialasiewicz / getty images after a while, white walls get blasé, and neutral rooms feel overplayed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Silver Pre Lit Christmas Tree 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/silver-pre-lit-christmas-tree-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/silver-pre-lit-christmas-tree-2021/</guid>
      <description>Get it before it&amp;#039;s gone. We may earn commission on some of. Cj our stunning saratoga spruce tree is perfect for welcoming guests to your home.
  5ft Silver Tinsel -Twig Christmas Tree by Sterling Tree Company from images.hayneedle.com  Walmart this amazing christmas tree will create a welcome, festive feeling for your christmas holiday. You know what a pre lit christmas tree means? Cj our stunning saratoga spruce tree is perfect for welcoming guests to your home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dog Santa Costume 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/dog-santa-costume-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/dog-santa-costume-2021/</guid>
      <description>As a dog owner, you’re bound to deal with a case of diarrhea at one point or another. We researched the best dog halloween costumes so you can pick a great one for your puppy. However, as any dog owner can attest, try as we might, communicating with our furry friends isn’t always the easiest.
  Cool Couples Costume: Mia Wallace and Vince Vega from Pulp Fiction from www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Outdoor Artificial Christmas Tree 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/outdoor-artificial-christmas-tree-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/outdoor-artificial-christmas-tree-2021/</guid>
      <description>We found stunning modern christmas trees that will refresh your halls and inspire you this holiday season. It&amp;#039;s an essential christmas item to stop trees toppling over. Dan faires creates an outdoor christmas tree made from reclaimed barn wood.
  Classic Theme Tree Ornament Package | Commercial Christmas Supply from cdn.shopify.com  Tree service companies take care of problems related to trees in urban, rural and forest settings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Dinosaur Inflatable 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-dinosaur-inflatable-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-dinosaur-inflatable-2021/</guid>
      <description>To help you shop for christmas inflatables that will actually stay up and stay put while. Put away the giant inflatable snowman, because a festive dinosaur in a santa hat and knit scarf has returned from extinction to invade your . Choose from same day delivery, .
  T-rex Dinosaurs Costume | Mascot Rental for Event &amp;amp; Children Party from mascotrental.com.sg  Led light up giant christmas dinosaur inflatable includes a 5 foot inflatable .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Holiday Card Sayings 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/holiday-card-sayings-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/holiday-card-sayings-2021/</guid>
      <description>With snow much love 8. Best wishes to you and your family for a happy holiday season and a wonderful new year. Wishing everyone at your home health, peace, prosperity, and happiness in the coming year.
  Heartfelt Thanksgiving Card | Birthday &amp;amp; Greeting Cards by Davia from www.holidaycardsapp.com  Best wishes to you and your family for a happy holiday season and a wonderful new year. Warmest wishes of the season from our family to yours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snowman Door Decoration 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/snowman-door-decoration-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/snowman-door-decoration-2021/</guid>
      <description>It is absolutely that you will hear “let it snow, let it snow, let it snow” lyrics throughout christmas time. 23/11/2021 · let it snow text with snowman on the door decorating. Please message me if you have any questions.
  2012 LEC door decorating contest - Bumble the A-Bonnie-able Snowman from i.pinimg.com  Then, why should we bring these famous words out to your door? Christmas classroom door with a reindeer head and the text merry and bright Add to favorites wood snowman door display/hanging snowman/ made per order not ready to ship jessicaspicketfence 5 out of 5 stars (966) star seller $ 30.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cute Christmas Cookies 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/cute-christmas-cookies-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/cute-christmas-cookies-2021/</guid>
      <description>Perfect sugar cookies · 2 of 94. Mini gingerbread men · 2 of 36. Chocolate kisses snowball cookies · 5 of .
  Cookies And Cream Ice Cream Pictures, Photos, and Images for Facebook from www.lovethispic.com  24 pretty christmas cookies with no pipping required ; 1 · chocolate dipped christmas sugar cookies ; Perfect sugar cookies · 2 of 94. · buttery spritz cookies · ugly sweater cookies · candy cane snowballs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gemmy Christmas Inflatables 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/gemmy-christmas-inflatables-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/gemmy-christmas-inflatables-2021/</guid>
      <description>4&amp;#039; lighted disney mickey and minnie christmas inflatable. With a passion for innovation, technology and creative design, gemmy has changed the . Don&amp;#039;t miss these amazing prices on gemmy.
  Pin on christmas and halloween and easter and thanksgiving wish &amp;amp; want from i.pinimg.com  Featuring a snowman, christmas tree and red snowflake archway, this charming inflatable. Gemmy christmas inflatable 12′ grinch on . With a passion for innovation, technology and creative design, gemmy has changed the .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hottest Gifts 2021 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/hottest-gifts-2021-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/hottest-gifts-2021-2021/</guid>
      <description>Our editors independently research, test, and recommend the best products; It’s hard to believe that 2021 is almost over. Evolution, like gravity, is still technically a theory, but recent evolutionary discoveries make this process of development seem ever more plausible.
  Ryder james | Hottest guy ever, My future boyfriend, Future boyfriend from i.pinimg.com  We&amp;#039;ve gathered the best housewarming gifts out there so you can be the best guest ever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4Ft Fibre Optic Christmas Tree 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/4ft-fibre-optic-christmas-tree-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/4ft-fibre-optic-christmas-tree-2021/</guid>
      <description>However, where did this traditio. To revisit this article, select my account, then view save. A christmas tree adorned with twinkling lights and ornaments is an essential holiday decoration.
  White Fibre Optic Christmas Tree with Multicoloured LEDs â Garden Trends from cdn.shopify.com  Participated in the home decor contest did you make this project? At christmas, i made a tree with magnets. This custom tree adds sophistication to your holiday decor and is super easy to stor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Song Religious 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-song-religious-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-song-religious-2021/</guid>
      <description>08/12/2019 · religious christmas songs and hymns playlist with lyrics featuring 27 christmas carols and christmas hymns. “noel” this is one of the beautiful christmas religious songs that celebrate the birth of jesus. “away in a manger” this song has exquisitely performed by the country singer martina mcbride.
  Early Learning Resources Mix a Pancake Poster from www.earlylearninghq.org.uk  30/11/2021 · top 50 religious christmas songs 1. “away in a manger” this song has exquisitely performed by the country singer martina mcbride.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Designer Christmas Cards 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/designer-christmas-cards-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/designer-christmas-cards-2021/</guid>
      <description>In addition to cash or credit, there is google pay, apple pay, paypal, venmo, and cashapp. Whether you are looking to apply for a new credit card or are just starting out, there are a few things to know beforehand. Obviously your business card should include your contact.
  8 useful Christmas card templates | Creative Bloq from cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net  Green card (also known as a permanent resident card) does that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pre Lit Pop Up Christmas Tree 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/pre-lit-pop-up-christmas-tree-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/pre-lit-pop-up-christmas-tree-2021/</guid>
      <description>Find all things home all in one place. 03/07/2021 · pop up christmas trees. Free horse coloring pages free letter c coloring pages free easter coloring pages free dinosaur coloring pages free peppa pig coloring pages free personalized name coloring pages for adults.
  The Disney Pop-Up Christmas Tree - Hammacher Schlemmer from digital.hammacher.com  12/07/2021 · pre lit pop up christmas tree. Free horse coloring pages free letter c coloring pages free easter coloring pages free dinosaur coloring pages free peppa pig coloring pages free personalized name coloring pages for adults.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thomas Kinkade Christmas Tree 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/thomas-kinkade-christmas-tree-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/thomas-kinkade-christmas-tree-2021/</guid>
      <description>This gorgeous tabletop tree showcases an entire thomas kinkade village, with 8 of thomas … Nothing matches a child’s excitement like finding a lionel train under the tree on christmas morning. Thomas kinkade christmas tree with lights, motion and music.
  2016 Christmas Screensavers - Wallpapers, Backgrounds, Pics, Images from wallpapers9.org  This gorgeous tabletop tree showcases an entire thomas kinkade village, with 8 of thomas … Thomas kinkade animated crystal tabletop … 11/12/2021 · thomas kinkade christmas tree.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elegant Christmas Tree Decorating Ideas 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/elegant-christmas-tree-decorating-ideas-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/elegant-christmas-tree-decorating-ideas-2021/</guid>
      <description>An elegant christmas tree will create a rich, welcoming feeling without overpowering the rest of your home. See more ideas about christmas tree decorations, elegant christmas trees, elegant christmas. 33 beautiful christmas tree ribbon ideas for your home.
  People Are Decorating Their Christmas Trees With Flowers And The from cdn.architecturendesign.net  These are some of the best christmas tree decoration ideas that make a statement. 01/04/2021 · elegant christmas tree decorating ideas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Poems For Kids 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-poems-for-kids-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-poems-for-kids-2021/</guid>
      <description>Beads from a craft store onto thick pipe cleaners, folded in half so kids can ea. They&amp;#039;re great for the whole family. Here are five great romantic poems to inspir.
  Country Rhymes - a classic collection of Outback Australian short from countryrhymes.com  Need a creative christmas class activity? Having famous parents comes with plenty of fringe benefits, like going to red carpet premieres and being able to score tickets to coachella.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unicorn Tree Topper 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/unicorn-tree-topper-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/unicorn-tree-topper-2021/</guid>
      <description>This will be a tree topper for a nightmare before christmas theme. It uplifts the spirits of people during the winter and carries the refreshing scents of pine cones and spruce. Here are 18 decorative tree toppers to buy.
  FIBER OPTIC PURPLE ANGEL TREE TOPPER from s.ecrater.com  Here’s more information on the jobs that tree service businesses. This will be a tree topper for a nightmare before christmas theme.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Large Christmas Balls 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/large-christmas-balls-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/large-christmas-balls-2021/</guid>
      <description>The balls make it much cooler, so even your kids love to have it. Extra large outdoor christmas balls, giant christmas balls for outdoor, oversized outdoor christmas decorations, jumbo christmas ornaments for outside, christmas outdoor giant ornament balls, oversized christmas ornaments outdoor, make giant outdoor christmas ornaments, extra large outdoor christmas ornaments taco bell 39 s roads that offer for … Large christmas tree balls for outside.
  20+ Most Beautiful Outdoor Decoration Ideas for Christmas - Noted List from notedlist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cookies For Santa 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/cookies-for-santa-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/cookies-for-santa-2021/</guid>
      <description>Make sure you&amp;#039;re ready for santa claus with these delicious chocolate chip cookies from blog quiche my grits. Santa&amp;#039;s favorite cookies are soft brown sugar pudding cookies, stuffed with christmas colored m&amp;amp;m&amp;#039;s and festive sprinkles. Soft and chewy double chocolate chip pudding cookies with m&amp;amp;m candies.
  Don Orione - TORTONA: Lâingresso del nuovo Vescovo Mons. Vittorio F. VIOLA. from www.donorione.org  17 best christmas cookies to leave out for santa · sugar cookies · gingerbread cookies · peppermint chocolate cookies · peanut butter blossoms · cake .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Tree Shop Online Catalog 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-tree-shop-online-catalog-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-tree-shop-online-catalog-2021/</guid>
      <description>Holiday christmas tree farm augusta nj jan 05.1min … Written byinesnov 24, 2021· 1min read. Catalogs com miles kimball catalog gift catalog free catalogs from pinterest.com.
  The In-Tree Christmas Train - Hammacher Schlemmer from digital.hammacher.com  Catalogs com miles kimball catalog gift catalog free catalogs from pinterest.com. Holiday christmas tree farm augusta nj jan 05.1min … Christmas tree shops flyer in 2021 christmas tree shop homeware furniture discount christmas trees from pinterest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pillsbury Holiday Cookies 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/pillsbury-holiday-cookies-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/pillsbury-holiday-cookies-2021/</guid>
      <description>Pillsbury holiday cookie earrings// pillsbury snowman cookie earrings. Hi cutiepies,today i am baking pillsbury holiday cookies for you guys!i have wanted to bake these for so long and for some reason never came . They&amp;#039;re really easy to just toss on a baking sheet if you .
  Yule Log Recipe - Pillsbury.com from images-gmi-pmc.edge-generalmills.com  Pillsbury serves a baking hack that will stop the cookie crumbles and make the holiday dessert pretty .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>9 Ft Slim Christmas Tree 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/9-ft-slim-christmas-tree-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/9-ft-slim-christmas-tree-2021/</guid>
      <description>9 foot christmas trees : Shop artificial christmas trees and a variety of holiday decorations products online at. See more ideas about christmas, christmas tree, christmas decorations.
  No. 2 Pencil Christmas Tree | Treetopia from www.treetopia.com  See more ideas about christmas, christmas tree, christmas decorations. The best 9 foot artificial christmas trees on the market. 9 foot christmas trees : Our 9ft christmas trees from christmas tree world are ideal for rooms with high ceilings and effortlessly create a cosy .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Gifts For Sister In Law 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-gifts-for-sister-in-law-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-gifts-for-sister-in-law-2021/</guid>
      <description>Inspiration is at hand with this christmas. 06/12/2021 · law funny in for christmas sister gifts. Find thoughtful christmas gift ideas for sister in law such as ventilated outdoor wine covers, custom camping mugs, 1 acre of land on the moon.
  Christmas Right/Left Gift Exchange Game &amp;amp; Poem - Uplifting Mayhem from www.upliftingmayhem.com  Find thoughtful christmas gift ideas for sister in law such as ventilated outdoor wine covers, custom camping mugs, 1 acre of land on the moon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Wish You A Merry Christmas Chords 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/we-wish-you-a-merry-christmas-chords-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/we-wish-you-a-merry-christmas-chords-2021/</guid>
      <description>G c we wish you a merry christmas, a/c# d we wish you a merry christmas, b/d# em we wish you a merry christmas g/b c d g and a happy . C g am g · good tidings . The chords for the song are f major, b flat major, g minor, c major, a minor, and d minor.
  We Wish You A Merry Christmas - Free easy Christmas piano sheet music from i.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crane Christmas Cards 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/crane-christmas-cards-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/crane-christmas-cards-2021/</guid>
      <description>Each year, crane showcase new designs with modern touches and hues. Get it as soon as mon, dec 20. Crane engraved christmas tree gift enclosure card, set of 16 enclosures.
  Collectable Dragon Skull from cdn.ecommercedns.uk  Send joyful tidings to family, friends and colleagues with sophisticated holiday greeting cards that capture your personality from crane stationery. Free shipping on orders over $25 shipped by amazon. Holiday penguins greeting card card 10 cards / 10 lined envelopes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minion Christmas Inflatables 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/minion-christmas-inflatables-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/minion-christmas-inflatables-2021/</guid>
      <description>4&amp;#039; gemmy airblown inflatable easter minion stuart holding an egg &amp;amp; paint brush. These mischievous minions try to climb discreetly on the roof to come and grab the presents! 9 foot tall inflatable despicable me carl .
  Tis Your Season | 4.5&amp;#039; Carl Minion with Scarf Christmas Inflatable from www.tisyourseason.com  Enjoy free shipping on most stuff, even big stuff. Indulge in the holiday spirit with fun &amp;amp; unique minion christmas inflatables at alibaba.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Friend Christmas Gifts Ideas 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/best-friend-christmas-gifts-ideas-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/best-friend-christmas-gifts-ideas-2021/</guid>
      <description>Looking to up your quarantine gaming habits? Everyone loves a great handmade present, especially when it’s clear how much time, effort and love yo. Best friends are there for you through thick and thin, so show them you care with these fun and practical gift ideas under $50.
  20 Funny Gag Gifts for White Elephant Party from styletic.com  Here are 10 unique gift ideas for employee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank You For Christmas Gift 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/thank-you-for-christmas-gift-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/thank-you-for-christmas-gift-2021/</guid>
      <description>Whether you need a holiday, thank you or appreciation gift for a staff member, there are a variety of fun gifts for every person on your list. The latest and greatest console from sony has some impressive specs — and, despite having just launched. Investment gifts that keep on giving we earn a commission for products purchased through some links in this article.
  10+ Creative Ruler Crafts - Hative from hative.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Polar Bear 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-polar-bear-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-polar-bear-2021/</guid>
      <description>Check out this fantastic collection of polar bear christmas wallpapers, with 40 polar bear christmas background images for your desktop, phone or tablet. Choose from same day delivery, drive up or order pickup. Directed by russ harris, g.
  Cute little Red Deer in a green grass-Desktop Wallpaper HD-3840x2400 from www.wallpapers13.com  Concrete polar bear ornament christmas decoration | xmas homeware gift. Choose from same day delivery, drive up or order pickup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Live Christmas Tree Stand 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/live-christmas-tree-stand-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/live-christmas-tree-stand-2021/</guid>
      <description>People have an innate curiosity about the natural world around them, and identifying a tree by its leaves can satisfy that curiosity. Start a new family tradition by planting a living christmas tree, so you can enjoy it for years to come. Here&amp;#039;s how to care for a living tree.
  Tree Topper Christmas Tree Topper Tree Toppers | Etsy from i.etsystatic.com  What is this chirstmas tree stand worth?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diy Christmas Garland 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/diy-christmas-garland-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/diy-christmas-garland-2021/</guid>
      <description>Whether it’s a table, kitchen wall or calendar, you can use numbers, letters or pictures to make any space your own. However, there are easier and less expensive way. If you’re planning any kind of party, decorations are one of the first things to consider.
  DIY Pine Cone Christmas Crafts That You Will Love from feelitcool.com  Many of us put off planning a halloween costume only to realize suddenly that halloween is just days away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Candy Cane Ornaments 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/candy-cane-ornaments-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/candy-cane-ornaments-2021/</guid>
      <description>#13 crystal science candy canes All you need is some green felt a candy cane and some craft bobbles such as buttons pom. Other ideas for using diy candy canes ornaments:
  25 Scandinavian Christmas Tree Decor Ideas - DigsDigs from www.digsdigs.com  Too many christmas ornaments can spell a disastrously overcrowded treeor inspire a great diy project. Free standard shipping with $35 orders. 26/11/2021 · how to make candy cane christmas tree ornaments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Cards Personalized 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-cards-personalized-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-cards-personalized-2021/</guid>
      <description>After a loss, it’s common courtesy to send a condolence card to the family to extend your sympathy. Whether you are looking to apply for a new credit card or are just starting out, there are a few things to know beforehand. Many across the world use debit cards to access their money for payments and withdrawals easily.
  Cozy Red and Black Gingham Pajamas in 2021 | Family christmas pajamas from i.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Wishing Card 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-wishing-card-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-wishing-card-2021/</guid>
      <description>Even if the rest of your card is printed, you should personally sign the card. Best christmas wishes to write in christmas cards. If you’re looking for ideas on closing remarks, find examples here:
  Christmas Bar Cart Ideas For Wishing A Warm Welcome To Your Guests from myamazingthings.com  May peace be upon you. Beautiful merry christmas wishes, christmas cards and ecards to share the spirit of peace and joy with your friends and family and make their christmas a memorable one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Funny Christmas Party Games For Adults 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/funny-christmas-party-games-for-adults-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/funny-christmas-party-games-for-adults-2021/</guid>
      <description>Every editorial product is independently selected, though we may be compensated or receive an affiliate commi. Rd.com holidays &amp;amp; observances halloween every editorial product is independently selected, though we may be compensated or. For example, you might be won.
  Facebook video of adults playing a &amp;#039;Poop the Potato&amp;#039; game at Christmas from i.dailymail.co.uk  I&amp;#039;ve been to many a party that focused on beer pong, and many (more recently) that centered around a snack table.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Cookies 2021 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-cookies-2021-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-cookies-2021-2021/</guid>
      <description>23/12/2020 · the holiday season brings the best recipes, and these christmas gingerbread cookies are a must try this season! In fact, cookies just need some type of sweetener to keep them … 1/2 cup gingerbread cookies instructions preheat oven to 350 degrees. Press the mixture into the pan.
  Norway Public Holidays 2021 - Publicholidays.no from publicholidays.no  Preheat oven to 350° and line 2 large baking sheets with parchment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photo Holiday Cards 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/photo-holiday-cards-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/photo-holiday-cards-2021/</guid>
      <description>They eliminate the need to carry around cash or checks. Some offers mentioned below are no longer available. If you’re having trouble coming up with the right words, a little guidance should help you write a short and heartfelt message to the surviv.
  Christmas Cards: Animated Images, Gifs, Pictures &amp;amp; Animations - 100% FREE! from www.animatedimages.org  With all of the new options, it can be easy to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merry Christmas My Friend 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/merry-christmas-my-friend-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/merry-christmas-my-friend-2021/</guid>
      <description>May god always protect you and love . Warm wishes on christmas to my pals . Christmas is celebrated as the birth anniversary of jesus christ.
  Merry Christmas From Our Home To Yours With Love Pictures, Photos, and from www.lovethispic.com  This is the time to spend time with your family and friends, singing christmas . Funny merry christmas messages for best friend. Merry christmas to you and your family!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gutter Hooks For Christmas Lights 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/gutter-hooks-for-christmas-lights-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/gutter-hooks-for-christmas-lights-2021/</guid>
      <description>Boost your brick walls with brick clips; Easily hang your christmas lights from your guttering, hedges or trees fill the outside of your house with lights with the help of these handy hooks. Keep your christmas lights firmly in place and ready to impress the neighbours with these gutter hooks.
  Multipurpose Accessories - Gutter / Shingle Clips, 25 Pack from cdn.christmaslightsetc.com  This 50 pack comes in handy when decorating the .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plastic Christmas Trees 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/plastic-christmas-trees-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/plastic-christmas-trees-2021/</guid>
      <description>The best time to prune is almost always when the t. There are three main reasons to prune fruit trees. And from a cozy afternoon spent hanging ornaments to a christmas morning brimming with presents, so much of the holiday season revolves around the tree.
  150+ Homemade Toilet Paper Roll Crafts - Hative from hative.com  People have an innate curiosity about the natural world around them, and identifying a tree by its leaves can satisfy that curiosity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>60 Inch Christmas Tree Skirt 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/60-inch-christmas-tree-skirt-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/60-inch-christmas-tree-skirt-2021/</guid>
      <description>Circle your tree with this plaid skirt, whic. Circle your tree with this plaid skirt, which you can sew in five easy steps. Find instructions, photos, and more christmas craft ideas on womansday.com.
  Sew Many Ways...: Tool Time Tuesday...No Sew Tree Skirt for $2.50 from 3.bp.blogspot.com  Almost nothing is as quintessential christmassy as a beautifully adorned evergreen tree. We may earn commission on some of the items you choose to buy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Engagement Ornament 2021 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/engagement-ornament-2021-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/engagement-ornament-2021-2021/</guid>
      <description>Follow this expert advice to refocus your team and keep them positive and engaged in 2021. Whether you prefer the convenience of an electric can opener or you&amp;#039;re perfectly fine with the simplicity of manual models, a can opener is an indispensable kitchen tool you can’t live without unless you plan to never eat canned foods. In november of that year, all of that work precipitated some exciting news:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jingle Bell Youtube 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/jingle-bell-youtube-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/jingle-bell-youtube-2021/</guid>
      <description>Listen to more of delta goodrem&amp;#039;s music here: Infobells presents this popular christmas song video &amp;#039;jingle bells, jingle bells&amp;#039;, enjoy this festive season to the fullest with this jingle . Jingle bells, jingle bells, jingle all the way!
  Fly me to the moon---Guitar,Piano,Flute,Violin,Trumpet--- - YouTube from i.ytimg.com  Provided to youtube by universal music groupjingle bell rock · bobby helmsthe best of bobby helms℗ a geffen records release; .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personalized Cat Ornaments 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/personalized-cat-ornaments-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/personalized-cat-ornaments-2021/</guid>
      <description>From history and biological anatomy to their behavioral patterns, there’s a lot to know about cats. Both have provided services and companionship to humans for many centuries. It&amp;#039;s adorable when your cat rolls over to show you her belly, but do you know why she does it?
  20 Creative Christmas Tree Ornaments - Style Motivation from www.stylemotivation.com  Despite their reputation for being dominant and independent, cats have effortlessly made their way into the hearts of many humans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oreo Gingerbread House 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/oreo-gingerbread-house-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/oreo-gingerbread-house-2021/</guid>
      <description>Whether you’re looking to buy your first house or moving into your dream home, buying a house always seems to take longer than expected. You&amp;#039;re going to want to try every single one of them. We may earn commission on some of the items you choose to buy.
  Gingerbread House Day 2019: Traditional and Alternative Kits from from d.newsweek.com  Every item on this page was chosen by a woman&amp;#039;s day editor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Masked Santa Ornaments 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/masked-santa-ornaments-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/masked-santa-ornaments-2021/</guid>
      <description>The most common mask santa ornament material is porcelain &amp;amp; ceramic. Youve seen the 2020 stink stank stunk grinch christmas ornament and you probably saw the family in face masks christmas ornament so now how about this hilarious 12 days of … 46 out of 5 stars.
  sale UK BATMAN (1940 Series) (DC) #670 2ND PRINT Very Fine Comics Book from i.ebayimg.com  Sale price $9.90 / quantity: 46 out of 5 stars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Activities For Kids 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-activities-for-kids-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-activities-for-kids-2021/</guid>
      <description>Whether your child is a budding genius or just a science geek fascinated by cool stuff, you can’t go wrong with fun activities at home that focus on science. Parents will plan parties and make their child’s favorite meal, but it can sometimes be difficult to know what exactly to buy them, especially if they seem to. Sel involves skills that build up a.
  Polar Animals | Fun Family Crafts from funfamilycrafts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Friend Christmas Wishes 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/friend-christmas-wishes-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/friend-christmas-wishes-2021/</guid>
      <description>One of the happiest times of the year. Find the right christian christmas card messages for friends and family with the list of greetings below. These are my wishes for you merry christmas our dear friends may you feel the love this special day.
  Happy Birthday Flowers Pictures, Photos, and Images for Facebook from www.lovethispic.com  Best christmas wishes for friends you find here and we hope you love it christmas is the most beautiful and delightful festive for the ones celebrating.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Gifts For Daughter In Law 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-gifts-for-daughter-in-law-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-gifts-for-daughter-in-law-2021/</guid>
      <description>We earn a commission for products purchased through some links in this article. Inspiration is at hand with this christmas. But can yours top the list?
  How to Cope With a Difficult Mother-in-Law from www.theadventurouswriter.com  Investment gifts that keep on giving we earn a commission for products purchased through some links in this article. Women&amp;#039;s health may earn commission from the links on this page, but we only feature products we believe in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Tree 4 Feet 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-tree-4-feet-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-tree-4-feet-2021/</guid>
      <description>Prezzie villa set of 5 feet christmas tree with 70pcs mixed decor + 6 santa caps + 6 santa masks for christmas party christmas tree and mini ornaments. You get one whiff of their crisp woodsy scent at the sidewalk stand and you have to have one. ₹2,589 save ₹290 (11%) get it by wednesday, december 22.
  Make Your Holiday&amp;#039;s More Colorful With This Rainbow Christmas Tree from odditymall.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Small Christmas Tree Stand 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/small-christmas-tree-stand-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/small-christmas-tree-stand-2021/</guid>
      <description>Country living editors select each product featured. A christmas tree﻿﻿ stand provides additional support to real and artificial trees﻿﻿ in your home. However, where did this traditio.
  18 Best Black Christmas Tree Ideas - Decorate Black Christmas Trees from hips.hearstapps.com  Learn more about the various types of cypress trees that grow in the u.s. There are three main reasons to prune fruit trees. Here’s more information on the jobs that tree service businesses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Decorating Fruit Cake 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/decorating-fruit-cake-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/decorating-fruit-cake-2021/</guid>
      <description>Use these simple cake decorating ideas/simple cake designs for birthdays or any other event by … :)get your cake and … In a large bowl, mix the marmalade together with the hot black tea and whiskey or orange juice until it had melted.
  Cotton Candy Cake 7 | Cake by Courtney from cakebycourtney.com  In a large bowl, mix the marmalade together with the hot black tea and whiskey or orange juice until it had melted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>15 Ft Christmas Tree 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/15-ft-christmas-tree-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/15-ft-christmas-tree-2021/</guid>
      <description>Display one in a vaulted living room to create a stunning backdrop for your holiday traditions. 8 and 8.5 feet tall; 9 and 9.5 feet tall;
  12/1/13 &amp;quot;WORLD&amp;#039;s TALLEST CHRISTMAS TREE&amp;quot; 115-ft, - YouTube from i.ytimg.com  Increase the beauty in your home with this residental christmas tree. National tree company 15 ft. 9 and 9.5 feet tall; 9 and 9.5 feet tall; Increase the beauty in your home with this residental christmas tree.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Tech Gifts 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/best-tech-gifts-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/best-tech-gifts-2021/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;#039;ve scoured the world for the best tech gifts under $100, so whether you&amp;#039;re looking for speakers or dro. Shop cheap tech accessories like a charging hub, portable bluetooth speaker and tech sanitizing wipes. Call it the holiday season, call it christmas, call it whatever you like, but the tradition is to r.
  Rolls-Royce isn&amp;#039;t making cars right now it&amp;#039;s making honey from www.driving.co.uk  With the price of tech always in flux, everyone is on the lookout for quality on the cheap.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Bell Ringing 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-bell-ringing-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-bell-ringing-2021/</guid>
      <description>And countless christmas gifts for children who would have gone without. Explore and share the best christmas bells are ringing gifs and most popular animated gifs here on giphy. Christmas bells are ringing, ringing in the musick8.com marketplace, home of music teaching ideas and music teaching resources for .
  Shamrock Rose Aussies - ï»¿ï»¿ï»¿ Welcome to Shamrock Rose Aussies!! :) We from shamrockroseaussies.com  Joy to all the earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fun Christmas Crafts 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/fun-christmas-crafts-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/fun-christmas-crafts-2021/</guid>
      <description>Heres how to sneak in some holiday spirit with the kids this december. Salt, paint, and some tape. Oh christmas tree, oh christmas tree… look at all these amazing christmas tree crafts!
  Egg Carton Train | Fun Family Crafts from funfamilycrafts.com  Then tie or glue them to an ornament base as a commemorative christmas bulb. I have been loving paper crafts lately! Fun christmas crafts for toddlers and preschoolers christmas crafts for toddlers … 09/11/2020 · make an elf apron: 09/11/2020 · make an elf apron: Salt, paint, and some tape.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baked Christmas Goods 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/baked-christmas-goods-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/baked-christmas-goods-2021/</guid>
      <description>Brownie christmas trees from suburban simplicity. 27/10/2021 · holiday baked goods are one of the best parts of the season. Looking for the best christmas gifts for 2021.
  Here Are The Top 17 Christmas Towns In Arkansas from cdn.onlyinyourstate.com  Brownie christmas trees from suburban simplicity. Get the recipe from delish. May village bakery is fairly new to the junction city area and is. So fun to find gifts for all my friends and loved ones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black Friday Christmas Tree Deals 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/black-friday-christmas-tree-deals-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/black-friday-christmas-tree-deals-2021/</guid>
      <description>Some of the best black friday mattress deals of 2021 are live right now, so don&amp;#039;t wait to try out a new mattress for a better night&amp;#039;s rest. 17 black friday christmas tree deals michaels 2021 ad best trees com cyber monday. 01/11/2021 · black friday christmas tree deals.browse christmas tree shops store hours and check out the best deals on the hottest products.
  Storming Crab Syracuse - Storming Crab Syracuse | Groupon from img.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021 Ornament Funny 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/2021-ornament-funny-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/2021-ornament-funny-2021/</guid>
      <description>However, this virus is still impacting countries and communities in an unpredictable way as infections co. Crossover vehicles are sporty and fun to drive. Undoubtedly, 2020 was a great year for fiction, with bestsellers like you should see me in a crown by leah johnson and the vanishing half by brit bennett.
  Custom Dog Ornament 2.75 Hand Painted Christmas | Etsy from i.etsystatic.com  Whether you prefer the convenience of an electric can opener or you&amp;#039;re perfectly fine with the simplicity of manual models, a can opener is an indispensable kitchen tool you can’t live without unless you plan to never eat canned foods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cornflake Christmas Wreaths 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/cornflake-christmas-wreaths-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/cornflake-christmas-wreaths-2021/</guid>
      <description>· scoop mixture into palm of hand . 1/2 cup unsalted butter ; 30 large marshmallows (about 3 cups) ;
  Christmas Treats Roundup - Tastes Better From Scratch from tastesbetterfromscratch.com  They are similar to rice krispie . They are green wreaths that mimic a holly wreath. · stir in green food coloring. 12g butter · 45g mini marshmallows (preferably white) · 45g cornflakes · green gel food colouring · red skittles/sweets or large red sprinkles for .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6 Ft Christmas Tree 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/6-ft-christmas-tree-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/6-ft-christmas-tree-2021/</guid>
      <description>To revisit this article, select my account, then view save. Professional appraiser helaine fendelman identifies and evaluates your collectibles and antiques. Linkshare vickerman 7.5&amp;#039; x 51 slim colorado spruce tree, 1680 pvc/.
  Complete Christmas Tree &amp;amp; Wreath Package (+ FREE Funnel) - #1 Christmas from www.o-christmas-tree.com  When it comes to christmas trees, i say the more the merrier. We found stunning modern christmas trees that will refresh your halls and inspire you this holiday season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grinch Tree Decorations 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/grinch-tree-decorations-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/grinch-tree-decorations-2021/</guid>
      <description>01/12/2021 · grinch inspired christmas tree legs pick green monster tree decoration with ornament grinch arm tree topper. Christmas grinch hand tree decorations, xmas grinch leg, head and hand, furry green, ornament stand, interesting ornaments, bendable hands jamierosecraft 4.5 out of 5 stars (499) sale price $33.15 $ 33.15 $ 39.00 original price $39.00 (15% off) free shipping add to favorites set of six (6) small grinch ornaments creationsbykellync 5 out of 5 stars (2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Make Christmas Ornaments 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/how-to-make-christmas-ornaments-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/how-to-make-christmas-ornaments-2021/</guid>
      <description>Everyone loves a great handmade present, especially when it’s clear how much time, effort and love yo. A christmas tree adorned with twinkling lights and ornaments is an essential holiday decoration. Country living editors select each product featured.
  21 Incredible Christmas Tree Decorations from www.topdreamer.com  Susan teare ©susan teare our best fall decorating ideas It uplifts the spirits of people during the winter and carries the refreshing scents of pine cones and spruce.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Red And Gold Christmas Tree Decorations 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/red-and-gold-christmas-tree-decorations-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/red-and-gold-christmas-tree-decorations-2021/</guid>
      <description>Christmas tree decorations gold and red 2021. 09/08/2021 · red gold christmas decorations.click the image for larger image size and more details. Place these gold reindeer around the dinner table for a magical woodland.
  32 Amazing Red And Gold Christmas DÃ©cor Ideas - DigsDigs from www.digsdigs.com  Much like the baubles, add a mix and match of gold and red or white to your tree, however, make sure the more extravagant, unique ornaments are red or white with different textures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Small Christmas Tree With Lights 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/small-christmas-tree-with-lights-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/small-christmas-tree-with-lights-2021/</guid>
      <description>In addition, many people use trees for landscaping, so it’s beneficial to know what species to look for wh. It’s nothing against real trees; Whether you prefer a warm glow or something brighter, shop the best tree lights here.
  Coolmade Small Christmas Tree with Lights, Mini Desktop Decoration Tree from i5.walmartimages.com  A christmas tree adorned with twinkling lights and ornaments is an essential holiday decoration. And from a cozy afternoon spent hanging ornaments to a christmas morning brimming with presents, so much of the holiday season revolves around the tree.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easy Christmas Decoration 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/easy-christmas-decoration-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/easy-christmas-decoration-2021/</guid>
      <description>We earn a commission for products purchased through some links in this article. Learn modern decorating tips from camille styles, a target style expert. Hgtv found the best neutral, modern christmas decorations under $25.
  Wonderful DIY Mesh Ribbon Christmas Tree from cdn.wonderfuldiy.com  Use these tips and tricks to make your cozy home feel spacious and comf. Add some unexpected colors and patterns with your christmas decorations to create fun touches that set the mood for the holidays.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Metal Tree Skirt 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/metal-tree-skirt-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/metal-tree-skirt-2021/</guid>
      <description>Use basic crochet skills to cozy up your christmas tree with a rope light tree skirt that looks amazing day or night. Every item on this page was chosen by a woman&amp;#039;s day editor. Use basic crochet skills to cozy up any holiday tree with a sweet tree skirt that looks.
  25 Great DIY Christmas Tree Stands And Bases - Shelterness from i.shelterness.com  Home outdoors garden if you’ve driven or walked down a street and spotted tree trunks wrapped with sheet metal, you may.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photo Frame Christmas Ornaments 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/photo-frame-christmas-ornaments-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/photo-frame-christmas-ornaments-2021/</guid>
      <description>04/05/2021 · christmas picture frame ornaments. The happy christmas photo frames are signed to show the love with holy jesses christ which was the messenger of god. There is a holiday in the entire world …
  Pin on | farmhouse WINDOWS from i.pinimg.com  The happy christmas photo frames are signed to show the love with holy jesses christ which was the messenger of god. Amazon com unomor 2018 my very first christmas ornament baby s first picture christmas picture frames baby first christmas ornament christmas ornaments gifts from pinterest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Tree Crafts 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-tree-crafts-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-tree-crafts-2021/</guid>
      <description>With help from these descriptions. The holidays are a magical time for kids—full of delicious smells coming from the kitchen, the sound o. Almost nothing is as quintessential christmassy as a beautifully adorned evergreen tree.
  10 Exciting Christmas Decorations Created From Pool Noodles - Amazing from www.woohome.com  We may earn commission on some of the items you choose to buy. In addition, many people use trees for landscaping, so it’s beneficial to know what species to look for wh.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Friend Ornament 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/best-friend-ornament-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/best-friend-ornament-2021/</guid>
      <description>30,336 128 featured decorate your tree th. Classic silver ball ornaments add interest. Then, choose between customized gifts the recipient is able to wear, use or display in.
  Disney Raya and the Last Dragon Raya and Tuk Tuk Ornament - Keepsake from www.hallmark.com  Author of ziger the tiger stories, a health enthusiast specializing in relationships, life improvement and mental health. He may look good enough to eat, but this sweet guy is really made of felt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gnome Christmas Tree 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/gnome-christmas-tree-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/gnome-christmas-tree-2021/</guid>
      <description>09/05/2018 · we’re including this video by the davis family to show you how they made their outdoor tree gnomes. Pull the hat over the upside down bowl to give it form. Diy gnome made with things from dollar tree including a mop,sock,twine,styrofoam cone and a christmas ball.
  Easy DIY Christmas Decorations for Outside - DIY Cuteness Simple Decor from diycuteness.com  Pull the hat over the upside down bowl to give it form.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>12 Drummers Drumming 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/12-drummers-drumming-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/12-drummers-drumming-2021/</guid>
      <description>I am very passionate drummer and i love the energy and power a drum kit transmits to the drummers and to anyone listening, so i decided to find a way to make that feeling universal. In this endeavor i salute you, especially if you’re a kid living at home with your parents (they will. Keeping your brakes working properly is an important part of vehicle maintenance.
  Bagpipes and drums &amp;quot; Amazing Grace &amp;quot; &amp;amp; &amp;quot; Highland Cathedral &amp;quot; by Mac from i.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cross Stitch Stocking 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/cross-stitch-stocking-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/cross-stitch-stocking-2021/</guid>
      <description>Learn how with our tips, patterns and tutorials. The spruce crafts / mollie johanson want to add color and design to your crochet without learning how to change colors for c. Cross stitch is the perfect solution!
  Princess Elliana Cross Stitch from stitchandfrog.com  Professional appraiser helaine fendelman has the answer. Sign up for marketbeat all access to gain access to marketbeat&amp;#039;s full suite of research tools: Country living editors select each product featured.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Painting Christmas Ornaments 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/painting-christmas-ornaments-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/painting-christmas-ornaments-2021/</guid>
      <description>Forster xl and xxl jumbo woodsie circles forster 2 large woodsies teardrops forster woodsies too medium triang. For many people, the kitchen is the heart of the home. This feathery penguin ornament is a great addition to any christmas tree.
  Penguin Hand-painted Wood Slice Ornament, by Our Backyard Studio in from www.theweedpatchstore.com  30,336 128 featured decorate your tree th. Learn two different ways to make your own tree decorations this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Send Christmas Cards 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/send-christmas-cards-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/send-christmas-cards-2021/</guid>
      <description>These cards have been in existence since the 1970s. And not just any cards, but cards with the wow factor. With all of the new options, it can be easy to.
  To My Long Time Friend - Happy Thanksgiving Card for Friends | Birthday from www.holidaycardsapp.com  Whether you are looking to apply for a new credit card or are just starting out, there are a few things to know beforehand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>T 38 Christmas Tree 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/t-38-christmas-tree-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/t-38-christmas-tree-2021/</guid>
      <description>This item isn&amp;#039;t sold in stores. Couldn&amp;#039;t understand why it was so cheap until we opened the box and realised its like a tree jigsaw! And while today&amp;#039;s faux christmas trees are a far cry .
  41 Beautiful Tabletop Christmas Trees - DigsDigs from www.digsdigs.com  This item isn&amp;#039;t sold in stores. This tree isn&amp;#039;t called “the world&amp;#039;s best” for nothing. If you haven&amp;#039;t “worked” with a flocked tree before, you must understand, .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diy Christmas Gifts For Dad 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/diy-christmas-gifts-for-dad-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/diy-christmas-gifts-for-dad-2021/</guid>
      <description>It can be difficult though to choose what to buy or make what is funny yet not offensive. Finding the perfect gift is hard, but using digital photos to create homemade or personalized presents makes it easier. Often this depends on your relationship with who it is for and the occas.
  30 Handmade Birthday Card Ideas from diyjoy.com  We&amp;#039;ve got diy christmas gifts for mom, diy christmas gifts for boyfriends, and other craft ideas for christmas presents!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Ball Garland 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-ball-garland-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-ball-garland-2021/</guid>
      <description>Before she became an iconic comedy star, ball was a struggling student and actress. Use these to decorate your home or use as a centerpiece. Use these to decorate your home or use as a centerpiece.
  Winter Christmas Background Scene With Red Element Stock Photo from media.istockphoto.com  Well, earlier this week i learned about a new product that totally solves this problem. Sit with a medium medicine ball on your left side, your legs bent on the floor, your left foot touching the top of you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Borders Free 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-borders-free-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-borders-free-2021/</guid>
      <description>You can find &amp;amp; download the most popular christmas border vectors on freepik. There are more than 42,000 vectors, stock photos &amp;amp; psd files. Stock photos decorative border picture.
  Luxury typography logo vector | Free download from cgispread.com  199 free images of christmas border. Christmas border clip art free. Download christmas cliparts border and use any clip art,coloring,png graphics in your website, document or presentation. 199 free images of christmas border / 2 ‹ ›.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Lover Gifts 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/tech-lover-gifts-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/tech-lover-gifts-2021/</guid>
      <description>Looking for a great gift for the techie in your life, but don&amp;#039;t want to spend a fortune? A bottle of wine makes a great gift for a wine connoisseur, but for a truly special person, you might want to go a little further than picking up a simple bottle of cabernet at your local grocery store. Whether you&amp;#039;re shopping for a techie or a kid, an adventurer or a gamer, it can be a challenge to keep up with what&amp;#039;s hot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Animated Christmas Greetings 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/animated-christmas-greetings-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/animated-christmas-greetings-2021/</guid>
      <description>In just a few minutes, you can create and . Send this merry christmas greeting card to your friends and family members. Send some holiday cheer with interactive christmas ecards.
  30 Merry Christmas Animated Gif Greetings - Best Animations from bestanimations.com  4k and hd video ready for any nle immediately. Funny christmas animation short films: Create your own animated christmas video greeting for free using animaker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home Depot Outdoor Christmas Decorations 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/home-depot-outdoor-christmas-decorations-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/home-depot-outdoor-christmas-decorations-2021/</guid>
      <description>Free delivery to your doorstep. Msi greecian white hexagon 12 in. Make the holidays magical with outdoor christmas decorations from the home depot.
  Fascinating Articles and Cool Stuff: Awesome Christmas Indoor Decorations from 2.bp.blogspot.com  24 x 80 hollow core interior doors. Make the holidays magical with outdoor christmas decorations from the home depot. X 10 mm polished marble mosaic tile (9.8 sq. Msi greecian white hexagon 12 in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ho Ho Ho Merry Christmas 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/ho-ho-ho-merry-christmas-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/ho-ho-ho-merry-christmas-2021/</guid>
      <description>Have a holy and a … With tenor, maker of gif keyboard, add popular ho ho merry christmas animated gifs to your conversations. Song from the album christmas and new years sound effects is released on dec 2007.
  25+ Hospital Christmas Decorations That Show Medical Staff Are The Most from cdn.architecturendesign.net  11/12/2015 · your favorite youtube stars wish you a merry christmas! Download ho ho ho from our ho ho ho christmas songs for kids album on itunes: Ho ho ho merry christmas!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Gift Ideas For Girlfriend 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-gift-ideas-for-girlfriend-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-gift-ideas-for-girlfriend-2021/</guid>
      <description>With baptism, your son will become a formal member of your church and begin a great journey in faith. Everyone loves a great handmade present, especially when it’s clear how much time, effort and love yo. These gifts are sure to put a sm.
  Best 25+ Lottery ticket tree ideas on Pinterest | Lotto tickets from i.pinimg.com  When choosing the right gift for a beloved family member or lifelong friend, you want your final choice to be something special.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Door Wreath 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-door-wreath-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-door-wreath-2021/</guid>
      <description>For some people, the garage door is the front door of their property because they drive their vehicle into the garage and then enter the house through a side door. The simple answer is “when it is ajar.” the riddle may seem straightforward, but it has a few complex details worth exploring. Each winter, front doors, living rooms, hallways and banisters alike usher in holiday spirit by bearing beautiful wreaths that deliver a fresh, green touch of the outdoors into homes across the country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Decorative Christmas Boxes 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/decorative-christmas-boxes-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/decorative-christmas-boxes-2021/</guid>
      <description>When it’s time to replace a fuse box, professional electricians are usually recommended for the job. Add some unexpected colors and patterns with your christmas decorations to create fun touches that set the mood for the holidays. People use safe deposit boxes to hold a variety of important papers and other items.
  Easy Christmas Holiday Centerpiece: Make in 15 Minutes from betweennapsontheporch.net  Because the uses are so varied they come in a variety of different sizes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Bedroom Ideas 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-bedroom-ideas-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-bedroom-ideas-2021/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to keep your bedroom cozy, neat, tidy and organized. No matter if you’re redecorating a child’s or a master bedroom, having design ideas are helpful. Add some unexpected colors and patterns with your christmas decorations to create fun touches that set the mood for the holidays.
  16 Brilliant Ideas How to Decorate Your Living Room for Christmas from www.stylemotivation.com  These small bedroom ideas will help you make the best use of available space without compromising on style.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Light Stakes 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-light-stakes-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-light-stakes-2021/</guid>
      <description>Buy noma candy cane pathway lights | pathway markers | christmas light stakes | 28” | set of 3 online at an affordable price. Roll over image to zoom . Christmas light stakes an easy way to accent the edges of your landscaping!
  72â³ LED Snowman â CostcoChaser from www.cochaser.com  Get special offers &amp;amp; fast . Alibaba.com offers 2851 christmas light lawn stakes products. Growing up, in our family, we knew that in order for our family christmas light .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Eve Mass 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-eve-mass-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-eve-mass-2021/</guid>
      <description>2 you have brought them abundant joy and great rejoicing, as they rejoice before you as at the harvest, as people make merry when … Please join us for our christmas services this year. The christmas eve mass has traditionally been celebrated in st.peter&amp;#039;s basilica.
  Celebrate the Second Week of Advent | CBN.com from www1.cbn.com  Pope francis will also celebrate christmas night mass this year on december 24 at 730 pm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Mailbox Decor 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-mailbox-decor-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-mailbox-decor-2021/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;#039;s how to decorate for christmas with ornaments you&amp;#039;re not using. Festive styling experts reveal their tricks of the trade to help you bring a professional finish to your christmas decorating ideas. Rd.com holidays &amp;amp; observances christmas this standout wreath is just a foam base with ribbons and ornaments wrapped around it.
  Fun &amp;amp; Festive Christmas Home from www.livingandlearningwithluisa.com  74 this is the simplest christmas decor, and looks great, whether it is in a window, or on your bathroom co.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What To Say In A Christmas Card 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/what-to-say-in-a-christmas-card-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/what-to-say-in-a-christmas-card-2021/</guid>
      <description>Try out these simple, meaningful messages. Happy holidays to a special friend who makes every single day sparkle and twinkle. May your christmas be bright and merry, my dear friend.
  Sparkling Christmas Tree Card | Birthday &amp;amp; Greeting Cards by Davia from www.holidaycardsapp.com  On the lighter side of the holidays, hip and modern holiday cards, funny christmas cards, and animal christmas cards are other ways to address your recipients this holiday season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diy Snowman Ornament 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/diy-snowman-ornament-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/diy-snowman-ornament-2021/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;#039;s how to diy the cutest snowman ornaments for your christmas tree, including steps and supplies. Do you ever feel that halloween creeps up on you or that you&amp;#039;re never actually ready when the day arrives? But instead of buying party decorations that are generic, impersonal — and maybe even boring — why not put your crafting skills to use and diy some d.
  35+ Creative DIY Christmas Decorations You Can Make In Under An Hour from cdn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whitmor Christmas Tree Storage Bag 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/whitmor-christmas-tree-storage-bag-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/whitmor-christmas-tree-storage-bag-2021/</guid>
      <description>This is the year you get organized *before* your tree arrive. Cheyenne is a freelance contributor for the spruce passionate about cooking, health, and technolo. Just buying the cheapest usually gets you a leaky, easily pierced bag, but brand names aren&amp;#039;t usually worth their price either.
  Best Christmas Tree Storage Bag with Wheels from ecx.images-amazon.com  We may earn commission on some of the items you choose to buy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Gifts For 1 Year Old 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-gifts-for-1-year-old-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-gifts-for-1-year-old-2021/</guid>
      <description>No matter if you’re celebrating a secret santa gift exchange during a holiday office party or if a staff member’s birthday is coming up, finding unique employee gifts makes these moments memorable. You can choose a useful gift or one to make them laugh out loud. These gifts are sure to put a sm.
  Christmas Pajama Party | Girls Night Holiday Pajama Party Ideas from i0.wp.com  Put down animal crossing and among us for a minute and dive into all things playstation 5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Funny Christmas Wallpaper 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/funny-christmas-wallpaper-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/funny-christmas-wallpaper-2021/</guid>
      <description>See the handpicked funny christmas wallpaper desktop images and share with your frends and social sites. Funny christmas wallpapers is a cool hd funny christmas theme wallpaper. Funny christmas santa cute merry snow craciun holiday winter hat red new year cat smile xmas.
  winter, Snow Wallpapers HD / Desktop and Mobile Backgrounds from wallup.net  See the handpicked funny christmas wallpaper desktop images and share with your frends and social sites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Religious Christmas Messages 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/religious-christmas-messages-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/religious-christmas-messages-2021/</guid>
      <description>See more ideas about religious christmas quotes, religious christmas, . May you are showered with the love and blessings of almighty in each and every . And i love at least one night by the christmas tree to sing and feel the quiet .
  Home Is Where The Christmas Heart Lives... Pictures, Photos, and Images from www.lovethispic.com  Wishing you a season of blessings from heaven above.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Thank You 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-thank-you-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-thank-you-2021/</guid>
      <description>Christmas thank you messages the christmas spirit of giving should be shown all year round, but especially during the christmas holidays. The time to send your love to your dear ones in form of short christmas wishes and thank you card messages. Merry christmas thank you messages 2021:
  Christmas Noel Sign Stock Image - Image: 3286201 from thumbs.dreamstime.com  That person has taken the time to invite you to something that was special to them, so it is only good manners to say thank you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wondershop Christmas Tree 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/wondershop-christmas-tree-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/wondershop-christmas-tree-2021/</guid>
      <description>There are three main reasons to prune fruit trees. Learn more about the various types of cypress trees that grow in the u.s. With help from these descriptions.
  Wondershop 42&amp;quot;- 54&amp;quot; Faux Fur Fluffy Brown/Grey Christmas Holiday Tree from i.ebayimg.com  It’s nothing against real trees; We found stunning modern christmas trees that will refresh your halls and inspire you this holiday season. If you’re trying to create a tropical oasis, you’ll definitely need a palm tree or two.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>December 25 Christmas 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/december-25-christmas-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/december-25-christmas-2021/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;#039;s the same game you love, but with updated visuals to celebrate saint nick and the summer solstice. Creating unique gift holders 01:00 think outside the box! When someone refers to the holidays, there&amp;#039;s a good chance they&amp;#039;re talking about an event in december.
  From Christmas to Diwali: Winter Holidays around the World - United from www.unitedplanet.org  In a way, december is the month in which everything is nominally on sale.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Gift Ideas For Dad 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-gift-ideas-for-dad-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-gift-ideas-for-dad-2021/</guid>
      <description>When they want or need something,. Gift giving is a happy event, but it might be especially tricky when the etiquette and expectations of the professional world apply. The latest and greatest console from sony has some impressive specs — and, despite having just launched.
  Personalized Poster 60th Birthday Gift from www.homemade-gifts-made-easy.com  *spends hours talking to relatives about which route to drive home* *spends hours talking to relatives about which route to drive home* buzzfeed staff, uk paying special attention to highlighting reruns of 1970s comedy shows and westerns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Cookies Delivered 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-cookies-delivered-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-cookies-delivered-2021/</guid>
      <description>All cookies &amp;amp; gift boxes are made fresh using the best ingredients. The image shows the man looking. A post shared by …
  Holiday Macarons Gift Box from Sucre - Always Order Dessert from 1.bp.blogspot.com  Cookie gift baskets and cookie samplers for delivery nationwide. The image shows the man looking. Watch till the end! the video is captioned. (aka everyone in the family will be able to find a variety they love.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Tree 5 Ft 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-tree-5-ft-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-tree-5-ft-2021/</guid>
      <description>Professional appraiser helaine fendelman identifies and evaluates your collectibles and antiques. Cj during the holiday season your home is not complete without the addition of a puleo christmas tree. 232 1 2 this design is a christmas tree made in a 3d printer.this tree is my best design in the 3d printer.
  15 Spectacular Silver Christmas Tree Ideas - Best Silver Holiday Trees from hips.hearstapps.com  When it comes to christmas trees, i say the more the merrier.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Holiday Sugar Cookies 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/holiday-sugar-cookies-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/holiday-sugar-cookies-2021/</guid>
      <description>Making decorated sugar cookies is a must during the holiday season, and these are the best sugar cookies you&amp;#039;ll ever taste. Making homemade sugar cookies is easier than you think. 1/2 cup melted shorting 3.
  Red Velvet Crinkle Cookies â Eat Well from canolaeatwell.com  Cover and chill dough for at least one hour. Left untreated, high blood sugar can be life threatening, leading to a diabetic coma.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good Christmas Presents For Girls 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/good-christmas-presents-for-girls-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/good-christmas-presents-for-girls-2021/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;#039;re looking for the perfect holiday cookie recipes, then check out womansday.com for desserts that will keep your tastebuds talking, like the gingerbread girls recipe. You may just find the perfect one for your b. Stuck for a great gift idea?
  Diy best friend gifts, 18th birthday gifts for girls, 18th birthday gifts from i.pinimg.com  If you prefer the latest baby names over very rare baby names, take a look at these ten.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dog Christmas Costume 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/dog-christmas-costume-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/dog-christmas-costume-2021/</guid>
      <description>Rubie’s walking elf santa’s helper dog &amp;amp; … Sold and shipped by the worthy dog. 99 ($6.66/count) get it as soon as thu, sep 30.
  Dr. Suess The Grinch Max Dog Antler pet cat dog Headband Costume Size L from i.pinimg.com  Dog king costume halloween costumes for dogs, dog halloween costumes with ruby crown king costume for dogs, dog cosplay costume for halloween christmas birthday party photo props.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Led Tree Topper 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/led-tree-topper-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/led-tree-topper-2021/</guid>
      <description>08/12/2021 · for the best look, you want to have some room between your tree topper and the ceiling. This led angel tree topper is a beautiful addition to any christmas tree décor. The top of your tree topper should be at least two inches below the ceiling, with six inches of space being ideal.
  How to Make an Angel Tree Topper: 48+ DIYs | Guide Patterns from www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reindeer Coloring Pages 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/reindeer-coloring-pages-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/reindeer-coloring-pages-2021/</guid>
      <description>Keep your kids busy doing something fun and creative by printing out free coloring pages. There are tons of great resources for free printable color pages online. Set off fireworks to wish amer.
  Free Printable coloring pages Frozen 2 - BubaKids.com from bubakids.com  There are tons of great resources for free printable color pages online. Includes images of baby animals, flowers, rain showers, and more. The set includes facts about parachutes, the statue of liberty, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3Ft Fibre Optic Christmas Tree 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/3ft-fibre-optic-christmas-tree-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/3ft-fibre-optic-christmas-tree-2021/</guid>
      <description>Fibre optic christmas trees are a great way to add some festive cheer without worrying about lights. However, where did this traditio. We earn a commission for products purchased through some links in this a.
  National Tree Company 3Ft Fiber Optic Firework Tree with Multi-Color from c.shld.net  Participated in the home decor contest did you make this project? 232 1 2 this design is a christmas tree made in a 3d printer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Target Open On Christmas Eve 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/is-target-open-on-christmas-eve-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/is-target-open-on-christmas-eve-2021/</guid>
      <description>Grocery stores open on christmas eve. Read latest news, news today, breaking news, india news and current news on is target open on christmas eve. Stay on top of the busiest time of the year with a clear plan.
  Last minute Christmas shopping? There&amp;#039;s still time! from x-default-stgec.uplynk.com  Now, please note they are not as available as on other days. Grocery stores open on christmas eve.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merry Christmas Best Friend 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/merry-christmas-best-friend-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/merry-christmas-best-friend-2021/</guid>
      <description>Merry christmas quotes for friend. Christmas is about having the best moments with family and friends. You deserve and will surely get a box full of blessings this christmas.
  Cheerful Snowmen Christmas Card for Friends | Birthday &amp;amp; Greeting Cards from www.holidaycardsapp.com  05/09/2021 · merry christmas to the best friend in the world the person that sees through my faults and loves me anyway. As the holidays approach use our best merry christmas wishes for friends to wish your companions the … I am so proud to call you a part of my family and i cherish the time i spend with you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Gifts For 6 Year Old Boy 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-gifts-for-6-year-old-boy-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-gifts-for-6-year-old-boy-2021/</guid>
      <description>5 30 sweet gifts for tween girls. If you buy something from the links on this page, we may earn a commission. Toyzone superman wave roller rolling scooter for kids 51657 from.
  Best gifts for 8-year-old boys - Cool Mom Picks from i979.photobucket.com  6 year old boy gifts for christmas 2021. Christmas gifts for 6 year old boy. It’s hard to believe that 2021 is almost over.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disney Christmas Tree Skirt 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/disney-christmas-tree-skirt-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/disney-christmas-tree-skirt-2021/</guid>
      <description>It uplifts the spirits of people during the winter and carries the refreshing scents of pine cones and spruce. Learn more about the various types of cypress trees that grow in the u.s. People have an innate curiosity about the natural world around them, and identifying a tree by its leaves can satisfy that curiosity.
  39133free christmas desktop wallpaper on SeasonChristmas.com | Merry from seasonchristmas.com  Native cypress trees are evergreen, coniferous trees that, in the u.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Bedroom Decor 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-bedroom-decor-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-bedroom-decor-2021/</guid>
      <description>74 this is the simplest christmas decor, and looks great, whether it is in a window, or on your bathroom co. Add some unexpected colors and patterns with your christmas decorations to create fun touches that set the mood for the holidays. But if traditional red and gree.
  painted dancing santa yard stake from www.atwestend.com  See our 20 favorite small bedrooms. 2,389 3 1 this is an ins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cornflake Wreath Cookies 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/cornflake-wreath-cookies-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/cornflake-wreath-cookies-2021/</guid>
      <description>· add marshmallows and stir until . How to make cornflake wreath cookies. Place it on the cookie sheet, using your fingers, press down and creating a hole in the middle, forming .
  Giant Christmas Wreath Cookie Recipe: Beautiful for Holiday Parties from i.pinimg.com  Cornflake wreaths are cute traditional christmas cookies. Instructions · pour cornflakes in a large bowl. They are green wreaths that mimic a holly wreath.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Die Hard Ornament 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/die-hard-ornament-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/die-hard-ornament-2021/</guid>
      <description>Tin foil, glue, scissors and a piece of wire. Strangely, there are not many decorations you can get for it. The first version of this ornament was made by imgur user …
  Best Homemade Ornament Ever from eatliver.b-cdn.net  23/12/2016 · we’ve all by now seen this excellent die hard christmas tree ornament, but since it got spread around virally so late in the year no one had any time to sell them (ahem, etsy).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St Nicholas Christmas Village 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/st-nicholas-christmas-village-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/st-nicholas-christmas-village-2021/</guid>
      <description>In may 1980, the largest terrestrial landslide ever recorded triggered a lateral blast at mo. Nicholas’s day in early december, when one of the older men at my church would dress up as st. Helens volcano erupted in 1980 and again in 2004, causing great destruction.
  Beautiful Fireplace Mantle Christmas Village - YouTube from i.ytimg.com  Read on for 10 interesting facts about mount st. We help you make informed decisions by giving you access to institutional quality data and analysis presented visually.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Gifts For 12 Year Olds 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-gifts-for-12-year-olds-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-gifts-for-12-year-olds-2021/</guid>
      <description>Find the best christmas gifts for your family and friends with good housekeeping&amp;#039;s christmas gift guides. You can choose a useful gift or one to make them laugh out loud. Here are 10 unique gift ideas for employee.
  Best Gifts &amp;amp; Toys for 9 Year Old Boys in 2014 - Christmas, Birthday &amp;amp; 9 from i.pinimg.com  These gifts are sure to put a sm. Whether you need a holiday, thank you or appreciation gift for a staff member, there are a variety of fun gifts for every person on your list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pillsbury Christmas Cookies 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/pillsbury-christmas-cookies-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/pillsbury-christmas-cookies-2021/</guid>
      <description>Christmas tree shape cookie dough (20 ct / 9.1 oz) at kroger. Roll the logs around pillsbury christmas cookie dough . Roll small dough balls with each type of dough, then roll the dough balls into long logs.
  Brownie Petits Fours recipe from Pillsbury.com from images-gmi-pmc.edge-generalmills.com  Shop for pillsbury ready to bake! Find quality dairy products to add to your shopping . Shop for pillsbury ready to bake!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Tree Farms In Maryland 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-tree-farms-in-maryland-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-tree-farms-in-maryland-2021/</guid>
      <description>We may earn commission from links on this page, but we onl. Native cypress trees are evergreen, coniferous trees that, in the u.s., primarily grow in the west and southeast. Wondering, where&amp;#039;s the best christmas tree farm near me? we&amp;#039;ve made it easy:
  Christmas Tree Farms Near Washington, D.C. from www.tripsavvy.com  Native cypress trees are evergreen, coniferous trees that, in the u.s., primarily grow in the west and southeast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Trees Led 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-trees-led-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-trees-led-2021/</guid>
      <description>It uplifts the spirits of people during the winter and carries the refreshing scents of pine cones and spruce. 232 1 2 this design is a christmas tree made in a 3d printer.this tree is my best design in the 3d printer. The project is going to have you fuse together all your plastic bags into a usable material.
  Starlit Trees - Bark from media.restorationhardware.com  With help from these descriptions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disney Christmas Wallpaper 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/disney-christmas-wallpaper-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/disney-christmas-wallpaper-2021/</guid>
      <description>Download and use 60,000+ christmas wallpaper stock photos for free. 01/09/2021 · disney christmas wallpapers for phones. You can also upload and share your favorite disney christmas wallpapers.
  Art Of Nature Arches National Park Utah Desktop Hd Wallpaper from www.wallpapers13.com  Hd wallpapers and background images Download and use 60,000+ christmas wallpaper stock photos for free. Explore and download for free tons of high quality christmas … 40000 high quality wallpapers backgrounds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coolest Christmas Lights 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/coolest-christmas-lights-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/coolest-christmas-lights-2021/</guid>
      <description>If you’ve got deep pockets and t. A list of some of the best holiday lights, christmas displays, and seasonal adventures in or near nashville during the month of december. Symphony of lights festivities like the winter festival of lights in watkins regional park, one of the most popu.
  Homemade Sparkle: 12 Awesome DIY Garden Light Ideas from cdn.wonderfuldiy.com  Steer clear of bright combos of green, red, yellow and blue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xmas Gift Ideas 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/xmas-gift-ideas-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/xmas-gift-ideas-2021/</guid>
      <description>Vaccines &amp;amp; 3rd doses | testing | patient care | visitor guidelines. Twelve holiday gift ideas for women. Whether you need a holiday, thank you or appreciation gift for a staff member, there are a variety of fun gifts for every person on your list.
  3e050b380caa47a620f323b925a6199a.jpg (736Ã981) | Auction gift basket from i.pinimg.com  Looking to up your quarantine gaming habits? Looking for the perfect gift idea for.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flocked Christmas Tree 6.5 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/flocked-christmas-tree-6-5-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/flocked-christmas-tree-6-5-2021/</guid>
      <description>It uplifts the spirits of people during the winter and carries the refreshing scents of pine cones and spruce. However, where did this traditio. There are three main reasons to prune fruit trees.
  The Holiday AisleÂ® Pre-Lit Flocked Green Fir Artificial Christmas Tree from secure.img1-fg.wfcdn.com  Learn more about the various types of cypress trees that grow in the u.s. To revisit this article, select my account, then view save.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jaclyn Smith Christmas Tree 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/jaclyn-smith-christmas-tree-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/jaclyn-smith-christmas-tree-2021/</guid>
      <description>Jaclyn smith shatterproof tree ornaments 12 999. Jaclyn smith christmas shatter proof blue silver white christmas bulbs icicles. Jaclyn smith trim kit midnight clear multi …
  Jaclyn Smith Christmas Tree Skirt Winter Wishes Light Lavender W from i.ebayimg.com  Jaclyn smith pre lit christmas tree instructions for secret santa! Amazon will be jaclyn tree assembly by cutting through the bottom section, often felled by the great inventions of lights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kids Ornament Craft 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/kids-ornament-craft-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/kids-ornament-craft-2021/</guid>
      <description>While it’s tempting to curl up with a laptop or fire up netflix on a day off, crafts are another fun way to get the creative juices flowing. Rd.com holidays &amp;amp; observances christmas “spending time together as a family is what the holid. The oxford english dictionary, published in the late 19th century, set the framework for dictionaries around the world.
  DIY Christmas Ornaments | Guide Patterns from www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Christmas Quotes 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/best-christmas-quotes-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/best-christmas-quotes-2021/</guid>
      <description>Want to make witty remarks this christmas? There is something about christmas that makes everyone feel spirited, happy, and excited. Sometimes all it takes to turn your day around is an encouraging word.
  15 Holiday Coffee Recipes That Will Keep You Warm This Winter from cdn.wonderfuldiy.com  Here are 10 famous quotes, life quotes you might want to remember. Use these quotes to inspire you to create your own christmas decorations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cheap Christmas Gifts For Kids 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/cheap-christmas-gifts-for-kids-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/cheap-christmas-gifts-for-kids-2021/</guid>
      <description>Whether you’re giving corporate gifts to employees or looking for small business client gift ideas, these o. The best holiday gifts under $10. All of them were independently selected by our editors.
  Bird&amp;#039;s Nest Craft for Kids | AllFreeKidsCrafts.com from irepo.primecp.com  They&amp;#039;re bound to love these! Gift giving is a happy event, but it might be especially tricky when the etiquette and expectations of the professional world apply.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baby Gate For Christmas Tree 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/baby-gate-for-christmas-tree-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/baby-gate-for-christmas-tree-2021/</guid>
      <description>Shop for christmas tree baby gate online at target. 11/10/2021 · baby gate for christmas tree. 30 fantastic christmas tree gate for baby christmas designs are generally put up in late november or very early december …
  Remodelaholic | Printable Christmas Decorations and Paper Ornaments from i0.wp.com  01/08/2021 · a christmas tree baby gate can be a saviour at christmas time when you have a toddler.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deer Christmas Decoration 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/deer-christmas-decoration-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/deer-christmas-decoration-2021/</guid>
      <description>12/08/2021 · reindeer ornament personalized reindeer christmas deer christmas decor deer reindeer door hanger reindeer ornament deer decor carolinagirlgiftsllc 5 out of 5 stars 162 star seller 1295. Festive card for winter event, party. Christmas decoration deer hanging from a tree.
  38 Stunning Christmas Front Door DÃ©cor Ideas | DigsDigs from www.digsdigs.com  A christmas decoration deer hanging from a tree. How to make a 3d reindeer christmas decoration reindeer decorations christmas reindeer decorations diy christmas reindeer from pinterest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>National Lampoon&amp;amp;#039;s Christmas Vacation Ornaments 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/national-lampoon-039-s-christmas-vacation-ornaments-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/national-lampoon-039-s-christmas-vacation-ornaments-2021/</guid>
      <description>2020 hallmark keepsake ornament national lampoon&amp;#039;s christmas vacation trimming the tree with sound available now for fast delivery. Christmas vacation clark griswold keychain. National lampoon&amp;#039;s christmas vacation 2021 hallmark keepsake xmas tree ornaments unboxing.
  Griswold Christmas Vacation village Dept 56 Display | Christmas from i.pinimg.com  Hallmark 3 national lampoon&amp;#039;s christmas vacation moose mug christmas ornament 2hcm9445 · department 56 snow village christmas vacation 20 pc 2021 mega set with .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top Men Gift 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/top-men-gift-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/top-men-gift-2021/</guid>
      <description>Looking to up your quarantine gaming habits? Gift giving is a happy event, but it might be especially tricky when the etiquette and expectations of the professional world apply. That’s one reason why it’s impressive that these famous actors have managed to carve out careers in a line of work where appearance is so im.
  10 Friendly Mustaches From the Cosmopolitan Archives from hips.hearstapps.com  Put down animal crossing and among us for a minute and dive into all things playstation 5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pink Christmas Decor 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/pink-christmas-decor-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/pink-christmas-decor-2021/</guid>
      <description>Michellealbert / getty images nothing brings about more joy than decking the halls for the holidays. This is an instructable on how to make christmas decorations. 2,389 3 1 this is an ins.
  15 Creative Christmas Tree Decorating Ideas from www.fantasticviewpoint.com  Pink is most definitely back, and it’s cooler than ever. Millennial pink may be popping up everywhere these days, but we’ve long loved decorating with the rosy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Tree Collar Skirt 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-tree-collar-skirt-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-tree-collar-skirt-2021/</guid>
      <description>Every item on this page was chosen by a woman&amp;#039;s day editor. With help from these descriptions. It&amp;#039;s also a perfect gift.
  BarnwoodUSA Deluxe Wooden Tree Box Collar Natural Weathered Gray from i5.walmartimages.com  Sure, a freshly cut christmas tree smells great — for a few weeks while you’re also dealing with the high cost, the hauling home, the dog drinking its water and the eventual crispy fire hazard it becomes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grocery Stores Open Christmas Eve 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/grocery-stores-open-christmas-eve-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/grocery-stores-open-christmas-eve-2021/</guid>
      <description>Breathe easy knowing you can shop at these convenience stores, grocery stores, and supermarkets on christmas day. Cash saver (hours vary by store): Many stores close early on christmas eve.
  Kroger Holiday Hours Opening/Closing in 2019 | United States Maps from unitedstatesmapz.com  Here are holiday hours for wegmans, tops and other grocery stores and several chain drugstores, from christmas eve to new year&amp;#039;s day: . Grocery stores open on christmas day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snowball Cookie Recipe 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/snowball-cookie-recipe-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/snowball-cookie-recipe-2021/</guid>
      <description>This is a wonderful recipe from colonial williamsburg. My husband grew up with this christmas cookie. The nuts are optional, if you l.
  Snowball Playdough Recipe and Free Printable Gift Tag - Yellow Bliss Road from www.yellowblissroad.com  These halloween cookies are easy to make and hard to resist! Every item on this page was chosen by a woman&amp;#039;s day editor. In a large bowl, stir together the sugar, ginger, nut.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baby Christmas Crafts 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/baby-christmas-crafts-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/baby-christmas-crafts-2021/</guid>
      <description>30/11/2020 · this is a cheap and easy christmas craft idea for kids. These are such a great selection of creative christmas tree crafts including popsicle sticks papers and handprints. Check out these creative christmas crafts for kidsyoull be sure laugh along the way.
  Crafts,Actvities and Worksheets for Preschool,Toddler and Kindergarten from www.preschoolactivities.us  18/09/2021 · baby christmas crafts ideas in 2021. Check out these creative christmas crafts for kidsyoull be sure laugh along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Front Door Christmas Decorations Ideas 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/front-door-christmas-decorations-ideas-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/front-door-christmas-decorations-ideas-2021/</guid>
      <description>For some people, the garage door is the front door of their property because they drive their vehicle into the garage and then enter the house through a side door. Add some unexpected colors and patterns with your christmas decorations to create fun touches that set the mood for the holidays. The simple answer is “when it is ajar.” the riddle may seem straightforward, but it has a few complex details worth exploring.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grinch Zoom Background 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/grinch-zoom-background-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/grinch-zoom-background-2021/</guid>
      <description>When you buy through links on our site, we may earn an aff. Whether you use it for your 10 a.m. Need to hide a messy room?
  The Grinch Newborn Photo Studio Backdrops Children Christmas | Etsy from i.etsystatic.com  These virtual backgrounds can replace the real background behind you. Be the first to discover secret destinations, travel hacks, and more. Zoom is one of the most popular video conferencing services on the internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Outdoor Blow Up Christmas Decorations 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/outdoor-blow-up-christmas-decorations-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/outdoor-blow-up-christmas-decorations-2021/</guid>
      <description>74 this is the simplest christmas decor, and looks great, whether it is in a window, or on your bathroom co. They say to not sweat the small stuff. Make your home&amp;#039;s exterior as festive as the inside with these outdoor holiday decorating ideas.
  Party Blow Up Christmas Tree Decoration , Giant Christmas Inflatables from www.kidsinflatablebouncehouse.com  763 11 by imi0827 in pallets by two paddles design in furniture by manfriend in backyard by enjoydiy in woodworking by jerryjaksha in backyard by watch me diy it in pallets by homemademodern in furniture by craftinista i.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7Ft Pre Lit Christmas Tree 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/7ft-pre-lit-christmas-tree-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/7ft-pre-lit-christmas-tree-2021/</guid>
      <description>232 1 2 this design is a christmas tree made in a 3d printer.this tree is my best design in the 3d printer. No more tangled lights.ever. shop the best pre lit christmas trees right here, including classic evergreens, white trees, and more, for every room size and budget. This design is a christmas tree made in a 3d printer.this tree is my best design in the 3d printer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rudolph Coloring Pages 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/rudolph-coloring-pages-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/rudolph-coloring-pages-2021/</guid>
      <description>And, not just rudolph alone, other deer that pull santa’s sleigh are also presented in these coloring pages. Find on coloring book thousands of coloring pages. May, a copywriter for the department store chain montgomery ward, which published the story as a promotional …
  Coloring Pages Rudolf - Coloring Home from coloringhome.com  11/09/2021 · 34 cute rudolph coloring pages for printing and coloring. Rudolph the red nosed reindeer coloring pages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Santa Costume Rental 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/santa-costume-rental-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/santa-costume-rental-2021/</guid>
      <description>Santa costume | prestige santa. The first thing to consider is the level of quality santa outfit offered as a santa costume rental. Claus costume with apron rent for $65.00;
  Costumes,Accessories for Costumes! from www.fantasycostume.net  The first thing to consider is the level of quality santa outfit offered as a santa costume rental. Nick costume rent for $75.00; We are now renting out one of the best santa claus costume available in malaysia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Gifts For New Moms 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-gifts-for-new-moms-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-gifts-for-new-moms-2021/</guid>
      <description>Christmas ideas for new moms, best mom gifts, best gift for new mom, christmas present for new mom, christmas gifts for new mothers, xmas gifts for new moms, 100 christmas gifts for mom, what to get my mom for christmas affectionately … New moms can often be held hostage in their vehicles for the sake of a good, solid nap. It includes a greeting card, kitchen apron, oven mitt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flocked Christmas Tree With Lights 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/flocked-christmas-tree-with-lights-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/flocked-christmas-tree-with-lights-2021/</guid>
      <description>Create a white christmas in any weather with a pair of sand &amp;amp; stable white fir artificial christmas trees. This prelit pencil artificial christmas tree will light up any room in your home.just take the tree out of the box, adjust the branches, and plug in the lights to get decorating right away!number of tall … You can also choose from traditional.
  Multiple Holiday Tree Arrangements, Modern Christmas Decor Trends from www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>White Christmas Tree Decoration Ideas 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/white-christmas-tree-decoration-ideas-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/white-christmas-tree-decoration-ideas-2021/</guid>
      <description>White christmas tree decorating ideas. 03/12/2021 · white christmas tree decorating ideas. White christmas tree decoration ideas.
  17 White And Silver Christmas Decorations â Creating A Snow Fairytale from www.digsdigs.com  Elegant christmas tree with silver ornaments and a gold topper. This reflects light and creates a soft glow. White flocked christmas tree decor 40. Elegant christmas tree with silver ornaments and a gold topper. This reflects light and creates a soft glow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7.5 Ft Pre Lit Christmas Tree 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/7-5-ft-pre-lit-christmas-tree-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/7-5-ft-pre-lit-christmas-tree-2021/</guid>
      <description>This tree comes with the convenient ez . Having a christmas tree included in your holiday celebrations is the best way to complete your celebrations. Experience the natural charm of medium 7.5ft artificial christmas trees this holiday season.
  Polygroup Ltd Polygroup LTD Pre-lit 7.5 ft. Artificial Quick Set Slim from c.shld.net  Need an artificial christmas tree? Free shipping to the contiguous us. When it comes to the perfect tree, you want to make sure you have the right size tree for your space .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>C9 Led Bulbs 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/c9-led-bulbs-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/c9-led-bulbs-2021/</guid>
      <description>Get the best deals on c9 led bulbs when you shop the largest online selection at ebay.com. New led christmas bulbs with the same bright, warm glow as vintage incandescent! Stocked in a rainbow of colors with added sparkle or an rgb morph, the deep facets of our…
  Wide Angle 5MM LED Lights - 50 5mm Multi Color Color Change LED from cdn.christmaslightsetc.com  These c9 bulbs have an intermediate base and .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Gifts Under 20 Dollars 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-gifts-under-20-dollars-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-gifts-under-20-dollars-2021/</guid>
      <description>Consider the recipient’s hobbies and interests. It’s hard to believe that 2021 is almost over. Find the best christmas gifts for your family and friends with good housekeeping&amp;#039;s christmas gift guides.
  The 28 Best Men&amp;#039;s Gifts Under $50 | The Daily Want from thedailywant.com  These gifts are sure to put a sm. Inspiration is at hand with this christmas gift guide for home lovers, gardeners, cooks, children and gadget lovers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finial Tree Topper 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/finial-tree-topper-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/finial-tree-topper-2021/</guid>
      <description>Both tree service technicians and certified arborists perform work on trees. A christmas tree adorned with twinkling lights and ornaments is an essential holiday decoration. Native cypress trees are evergreen, coniferous trees that, in the u.s., primarily grow in the west and southeast.
  Frosted Holiday Snowflake Tree Topper | Frontgate | Elegant christmas from i.pinimg.com  Nightmare before christmas halloween tree topper : What is 3d printing good for?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Owl Tree Toppers 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/owl-tree-toppers-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/owl-tree-toppers-2021/</guid>
      <description>Jim richmond/flickr/cc by 2.0 owls are some of the most fascinating and mysterious raptors in the world. How much do you know about owls? Mark newman / getty images owls have been part of human culture and mythology for millennia, viewed.
  Christmas Gift Giving FREE Printables - Onion Rings &amp;amp; Things from www.onionringsandthings.com  Here are 18 decorative tree toppers to buy. There is something about owls that fascinates people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Gift Ideas 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/tech-gift-ideas-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/tech-gift-ideas-2021/</guid>
      <description>With the price of tech always in flux, everyone is on the lookout for quality on the cheap. The latest and greatest console from sony has some impressive specs — and, despite having just launched. The holiday shopping season is in full swing and while you’ve likely already started checking several names off your list, you may be struggling with ideas when it comes to th.
  Wine Country Gift Baskets â New Yearâs Gifts Baskets from ww1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cute Ugly Christmas Sweater 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/cute-ugly-christmas-sweater-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/cute-ugly-christmas-sweater-2021/</guid>
      <description>Plus as an extra bonus, we created the cutest free printables for you to host your very own ugly christmas sweater party! If you like being funny during the holidays, ugly christmas sweaters are for you. You take an older cardigan and cover it in tensile and other festive yet gaudy décor.
  51 Ugly Christmas Sweater Ideas So You Can Be Gaudy and Festive from cdn.morningchores.com  Plus as an extra bonus, we created the cutest free printables for you to host your very own ugly christmas sweater party!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wood Turned Christmas Ornaments 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/wood-turned-christmas-ornaments-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/wood-turned-christmas-ornaments-2021/</guid>
      <description>Start with the basics in our guide. Plus, get our tips for displaying the christmas ornaments on your holiday tree. Ariel skelley/getty images watching an experienced woodturner develop and form an exquisite bowl, spindle or other turning from a block of raw.
  how to turn christmas ornaments - Woodworking Talk - Woodworkers Forum from www.woodworkingtalk.com  How to lathe and turn wood: Pair wooden accents with a bright tassel for a fresh take on beaded christmas ornaments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Decorative Wreath Ideas 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/decorative-wreath-ideas-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/decorative-wreath-ideas-2021/</guid>
      <description>See more ideas about wreaths, diy wreath, door decorations. Here, a branch decorated with crab apples brings a . The frugal homemaker&amp;#039;s board decorating:
  30 Spectacular Front Door Decoration Ideas for Christmas and Winter from www.lushome.com  Christmas decoration starts with decorating your front doors, and it can be popularly done with the christmas wreaths. Here, a branch decorated with crab apples brings a . Living wreaths are a great option to add some .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Artificial Palm Tree With Lights 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/artificial-palm-tree-with-lights-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/artificial-palm-tree-with-lights-2021/</guid>
      <description>Graceful curved trunk creates a unique, authentic look. Lighted artificial palm tree with 56 warm white led mini lights circling the trunk and 72 green led mini lights sprinkled throughout the canopy. 01/12/2021 · shop target for twig tree with lights you will love at great low prices.
  Christmas Icicle Light - 150 Red/Clear Frost/Blue Icicle Lights - White from cdn.christmaslightsetc.com  Made with pvc and other fire retardant materials.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Art Kids 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-art-kids-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-art-kids-2021/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to make family trees, herb collages, and many more easy art projects for kids. Having famous parents comes with plenty of fringe benefits, like going to red carpet premieres and being able to score tickets to coachella. Crafts help kids show their creative side.
  40+ Easy And Cheap DIY Christmas Crafts Kids Can Make | Architecture from cdn.architecturendesign.net  Shari finger &amp;amp; susan tumblety nail art for kids puts creativity at kids&amp;#039; f.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Trivia For Kids 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-trivia-for-kids-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-trivia-for-kids-2021/</guid>
      <description>When you want to make sure your children are watching eng. Dolphins are one of the more beloved animals in the world for people of all ages, but most people, particularly younger ones, might not know much about them beyond the shows they see at aquariums. The software helps kids and their parents and teachers find books at.
  Canada Facts for Kids | Facts about Canada | Family Travel | Geography from www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Tree With Led Lights 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-tree-with-led-lights-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-tree-with-led-lights-2021/</guid>
      <description>15,852 41 13 featured a nifty little led christmas tree made from nothing but leds, resistors, and a found power supply. It’s nothing against real trees; Sure, a freshly cut christmas tree smells great — for a few weeks while you’re also dealing with the high cost, the hauling home, the dog drinking its water and the eventual crispy fire hazard it becomes.
  Cool White LED Christmas Light Ball, Fold Flat Brown Frame from cdn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Presents Under Tree 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-presents-under-tree-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-presents-under-tree-2021/</guid>
      <description>However, where did this traditio. Here’s more information on the jobs that tree service businesses. Matt bliss rediscovered his grandfather&amp;#039;s playful designs from the &amp;#039;60s, and decided to share them with the world to revisit this article, visit my profile, then view saved stories.
  Christmas presents under the tree | Christmas presents underâ¦ | Flickr from live.staticflickr.com  With a wide array of palm tree varieties, you’ve got lots to consider before you buy a palm tree for your yard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skinny Pre Lit Christmas Tree 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/skinny-pre-lit-christmas-tree-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/skinny-pre-lit-christmas-tree-2021/</guid>
      <description>Walmart this amazing christmas tree will create a welcome, festive feeling for your christmas holiday. However, where did this traditio. It is perfect for an.
  No. 2 Pencil Artificial Christmas Tree | Treetopia from www.treetopia.com  Cj our stunning saratoga spruce tree is perfect for welcoming guests to your home. We found stunning modern christmas trees that will refresh your halls and inspire you this holiday season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Card Words 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-card-words-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-card-words-2021/</guid>
      <description>If you’re having trouble coming up with the right words, a little guidance should help you write a short and heartfelt message to the surviv. For some extra security to fall back on if times get tough or to help build y. While running up credit card debt you can’t immediately pay off is generally not a good idea, you may simply need a new ca.
  Good Luck Ecard Words - Crazecards from crazecards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Christmas Gifts For Women 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/best-christmas-gifts-for-women-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/best-christmas-gifts-for-women-2021/</guid>
      <description>These gifts are sure to put a sm. We may earn a commission through links on our site. You can choose a useful gift or one to make them laugh out loud.
  Christmas gift guide. Best buys under Â£25 | Sportsister from www.sportsister.com  Finding the best christmas gift ideas for her this year can be a challenge, but we found the most romantic and unique gifts for women this holiday season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dyker Heights Christmas Lights Tour 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/dyker-heights-christmas-lights-tour-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/dyker-heights-christmas-lights-tour-2021/</guid>
      <description>In addition to the dyker heights christmas decorations, the best in nyc, you will visit d.u.m.b.o. Don’t settle for cheap imitations. Dyker heights christmas bus tour is the most extravagant christmas light tour which is located in the dyker heights section of brooklyn is the most authentic tour of the area.
  Visit Dyker Heights Christmas Lights: All The Info â New Yorker Tips from www.newyorkertips.com  In addition to the dyker heights christmas decorations, the best in nyc, you will visit d.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Gifts For The Homeless 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-gifts-for-the-homeless-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-gifts-for-the-homeless-2021/</guid>
      <description>Here are 10 unique gift ideas for employee. What better way is there to perk up. The latest and greatest console from sony has some impressive specs — and, despite having just launched.
  New at Hm: Christmas Decorations and More! | Hm etc. from blog.homemakers.com  Looking to up your quarantine gaming habits? Consider the recipient’s hobbies and interests. You can choose a useful gift or one to make them laugh out loud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snowflake Tree Topper 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/snowflake-tree-topper-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/snowflake-tree-topper-2021/</guid>
      <description>However, where did this traditio. Its jack skeleton he makes a great tree topper. In addition, many people use trees for landscaping, so it’s beneficial to know what species to look for wh.
  Wonderful DIY Book Page Christmas Ornaments from cdn.wonderfuldiy.com  Here are 18 decorative tree toppers to buy. These are the first shoes that carry allbirds’ new sole, made from sustainably sourced sugar. People have an innate curiosity about the natural world around them, and identifying a tree by its leaves can satisfy that curiosity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iris Christmas Tree Storage Box 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/iris-christmas-tree-storage-box-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/iris-christmas-tree-storage-box-2021/</guid>
      <description>A christmas tree adorned with twinkling lights and ornaments is an essential holiday decoration. They can grow in zones two through nine and require si. My wife is a christmas decorating fanatic.
  Christmas Tree Storage Bag- Heavy Duty 58&amp;quot;x24&amp;quot;x34&amp;quot; Storage Container from i5.walmartimages.com  To revisit this article, select my account, then view save. However, where did this traditio. Boxelder trees are maple trees that produce very little maple.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>9 Slim Christmas Tree 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/9-slim-christmas-tree-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/9-slim-christmas-tree-2021/</guid>
      <description>Hobby lobby arts and crafts stores … 13/09/2021 · slim christmas tree 9ft. 26/11/2021 · nearly natural 9 ft.
  Red Artificial Christmas Tree | Treetopia from www.treetopia.com  Free shipping on orders over $19. Hobby lobby arts and crafts stores … 17/03/2021 · quick set slim yuletide pine christmas tree 9 hobby lobby 5064514 hobby lobby 9ft pre lit christmas tree in mooresville offerup it was worth the hunt love this christmas tree between naps on porch christmas decor world archiv 9ft premium snow flocked hinged artificial tree home with metal stand christmas decor world noma.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Grinch Background 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/the-grinch-background-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/the-grinch-background-2021/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to free wallpaper and background picture community. While it&amp;#039;s been 20 years since jim carrey first terrorized whoville as the grinch, mt. Check out this fantastic collection of grinch wallpapers, with 39 grinch background images for your desktop, phone or tablet.
  Wallpaper How the Grinch Stole Christmas, Grinch, green, Movies #10336 from wallpapershome.com  Install my the grinch new tab themes and enjoy varied hd wallpapers of the grinch, everytime you open a new.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Coloring Pages For Adults 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-coloring-pages-for-adults-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-coloring-pages-for-adults-2021/</guid>
      <description>Whitepages is a residential phone book you can use to look up individuals. Take a deep breath and relax with these free mandala coloring pages just for the adults. Because after all, everyone needs to decompress.
  Nightmare Before Christmas Characters Coloring Pages - Coloring Home from coloringhome.com  These alphabet coloring sheets will help little ones identify uppercase and lowercase versions of each letter. This collection includes mandalas, florals, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Truck With Christmas Tree 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/truck-with-christmas-tree-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/truck-with-christmas-tree-2021/</guid>
      <description>To revisit this article, select my account, then view save. And from a cozy afternoon spent hanging ornaments to a christmas morning brimming with presents, so much of the holiday season revolves around the tree. Almost nothing is as quintessential christmassy as a beautifully adorned evergreen tree.
  100+ Of The Most Creative DIY Christmas Trees Ever | Architecture &amp;amp; Design from cdn.architecturendesign.net  Here’s more information on the jobs that tree service businesses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Gifts For 5 Year Old Boy 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-gifts-for-5-year-old-boy-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-gifts-for-5-year-old-boy-2021/</guid>
      <description>Sections show more follow today more brands our editors independently selec. Sections show more follow today more brands our editors independently select. It’s hard to believe that 2021 is almost over.
  gift guide for 2 year olds- outdoor toys | Kids&amp;#039; Activities | Pinterest from s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com  According to the cia, as of 2018 there were an estimated 981,129,427 boys ages 0 to 14 living in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Tree Shop Coupon 2021 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-tree-shop-coupon-2021-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-tree-shop-coupon-2021-2021/</guid>
      <description>Not everyone feels the same way about when to put up a christmas tree, and there are valid reasons behind each tradition. Ribbon never fails to enhance decor for the holidays﻿. Our editors independently research, test, and recommend the best products;
  2 New Old Spice Coupons â Save $2 + Deals at Walmart &amp;amp; CVS | Living from www.livingrichwithcoupons.com  Our editors independently research, test, and recommend the best products; We researched the best christmas tree toppers, from angels to stars and snowflakes to bows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jack Skellington Clipart 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/jack-skellington-clipart-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/jack-skellington-clipart-2021/</guid>
      <description>You can filter jack skellington images by transparent, by license and by . New users enjoy 60% off. Download 21 jack skellington stock illustrations, vectors &amp;amp; clipart for free or amazingly low rates!
  Pin on Cutting Files from i.pinimg.com  Jack skellington and jack skellington face, jack skellington christmas transparent png. 267 jack skellington clip art. You can filter jack skellington images by transparent, by license and by .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good Christmas Gifts For Dad 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/good-christmas-gifts-for-dad-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/good-christmas-gifts-for-dad-2021/</guid>
      <description>*spends hours talking to relatives about which route to drive home* *spends hours talking to relatives about which route to drive home* buzzfeed staff, uk paying special attention to highlighting reruns of 1970s comedy shows and westerns. Moms, dads, friends, family, and more, including cheap gifts under $25. With baptism, your son will become a formal member of your church and begin a great journey in faith.
  Perfect Gift Ideas for Your Best Friends from ofriendly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Santa Face Clipart 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/santa-face-clipart-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/santa-face-clipart-2021/</guid>
      <description>Download in under 30 seconds. Free cliparts that you can download to you computer and use in your designs. Free santa face png images, face, clock face, face powder, north face, santa claus, poker face, man without a face.
  Grinch Head SVG PNG and DXF | Grinch christmas tree, Grinch christmas from i.pinimg.com  To explore more similar hd image on pngitem. All of these santa face resources are for free download .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Garland Decorations 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-garland-decorations-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-garland-decorations-2021/</guid>
      <description>Decorate your home for christmas using glasses, ornaments, and other items that you already own. 2,389 3 1 this is an ins. Cardstock this paper town will transform you.
  35+ Creative DIY Christmas Decorations You Can Make In Under An Hour from cdn.architecturendesign.net  Learn modern decorating tips from camille styles, a target style expert. Festive styling experts reveal their tricks of the trade to help you bring a professional finish to your christmas decorating ideas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Modern Christmas Decor 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/modern-christmas-decor-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/modern-christmas-decor-2021/</guid>
      <description>Before we go any further, i want to give you 21 organic modern christmas interior decorating elements to consider. Alternative christmas tree by elle decor #3. For parties, i’ll add lots of twinkling votive candles, a few flowers, and a bottle of good red.
  36 Super Elegant Black And Gold Christmas DÃ©cor Ideas - DigsDigs from www.digsdigs.com  Modern christmas candle holder | source #3. 26/11/2021 · when it comes to modern christmas decorating ideas, you can pretty much always turn to scandinavian design inspo to lead you towards those minimalist yet cozy vibes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Gifts Ideas For Friends 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-gifts-ideas-for-friends-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/christmas-gifts-ideas-for-friends-2021/</guid>
      <description>We may earn commission from links on this page, but we only recommend products we back. No matter if you’re celebrating a secret santa gift exchange during a holiday office party or if a staff member’s birthday is coming up, finding unique employee gifts makes these moments memorable. Whether you need a holiday, thank you or appreciation gift for a staff member, there are a variety of fun gifts for every person on your list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whimsical Christmas Decorations 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/whimsical-christmas-decorations-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/whimsical-christmas-decorations-2021/</guid>
      <description>2,389 3 1 this is an ins. Decorate your home for christmas using glasses, ornaments, and other items that you already own. This is an instructable on how to make christmas decorations.
  Fresh Cedar Garland â Friday Favorites â Petite Haus from www.petitehaus.com  But if traditional red and gree. Decorate your home for christmas using glasses, ornaments, and other items that you already own. We earn a commission for products purchased through some links in this article.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Play Jingle Bells 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/play-jingle-bells-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/play-jingle-bells-2021/</guid>
      <description>Learn to play seven simple kids songs on your piano or keyboard. Your browser can&amp;#039;t play this video. Your browser can&amp;#039;t play this video.
  How to play &amp;quot;Jingle Bells&amp;quot; piano - from &amp;quot;ABC 123 Doremi&amp;quot; game - YouTube from i.ytimg.com  Simple piano songs with letters for piano players . Simple kids songs for beginner piano players. They&amp;#039;re such an important element in making the piano fun for kids!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6 Ft Pre Lit Christmas Tree 2021</title>
      <link>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/6-ft-pre-lit-christmas-tree-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://angelajholmes.github.io/post/6-ft-pre-lit-christmas-tree-2021/</guid>
      <description>Artificial christmas trees · 7ft pre lit forest pine christmas tree · 7ft forest pine christmas tree · 7ft pre lit snowy christmas tree · 6ft forest pine christmas . Because of our every 6 ft christmas tree&amp;#039;s design and elegance, . Marvel at balsam hill&amp;#039;s collection of 4 to 5 foot artficial christmas trees made to fit smaller spaces.
  6&amp;#039; POP UP CHRISTMAS TREE PRE-LIT 250 CLEAR LIGHTS RED TINSEL PULL UP from i.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
